Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series LXXIV. WAGES
  - Sub-Series 408-0. Wages
    - General. Improvement Factor. New York Wage Increase Hearing. Employees' Exhibit No. 6. "Statistical Tables in Rebuttal", 1953 (Box 538, Folder 9)
    - General. Improvement Factor. New York Wage Increase Hearing. Employees' Exhibit No. 5. "Rebuttal Exhibit: Railroad Financial Data", 1953 (Box 538, Folder 10)
    - General. Improvement Factor. New York Wage Increase Hearing. Carriers' Exhibit No. 12. "Productivity and Wages", 1953 (Box 538, Folder 11)
    - General. Improvement Factor. New York Wage Increase Hearing. Carriers' Exhibits Nos. 1-12., 1953 (Box 538, Folder 12)
    - General. Improvement Factor. New York Wage Increase Hearing. Employees' Exhibits Nos. 1-6., 1953 (Box 538, Folder 13)
    - General. Improvement Factor. New York Wage Increase Hearing. Carriers' Exhibit No. 13. "Summary of Productivity Increases Approved by the National Wage Stabilization Board, June 1951-August 20, 1952", 1953 (Box 538, Folder 14)
    - General. Improvement Factor. New York Wage Increase Hearing. Carriers' Exhibit No. 1. "Railroad Employees and Their Earnings", 1953 (Box 538, Folder 15)
    - General. Improvement Factor. New York Wage Increase Hearing. Memorandum Agreement, Order of Railway Conductors Case, 1953 (Box 538, Folder 16)
    - General. Improvement Factor. New York Wage Increase Hearing. Memorandum Agreement, Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers Case, 1953 (Box 538, Folder 17)
    - General. Improvement Factor. New York Wage Increase Hearing. Carriers' Exhibit (not numbered). Railroad Employees' Earnings And Wage Increases Compared with Workers in Other Industries, 1953 (Box 538, Folder 18)
    - General. Improvement Factor. New York Wage Increase Hearing. Carriers' Exhibit No. 6. "Railroad Operating Results and Financial Situation", 1953 (Box 538, Folder 19)
    - General. Improvement Factor. New York Wage Increase Hearing. Carriers' Exhibit No. 7. "Traffic Evidence", 1953 (Box 538, Folder 20)
    - General. Improvement Factor. New York Wage Increase Hearing. Carriers' Exhibit No. 8. Map of Pennsylvania Railroad Routes, 1953 (Box 538, Folder 21)
    - General. Improvement Factor. New York Wage Increase Hearing. Carriers' Exhibit No. 9. "Practical Aspects of the Productivity Wage Increase Question", 1953 (Box 538, Folder 22)
    - General. Improvement Factor. New York Wage Increase Hearing. Carriers' Exhibit A, 1953 (Box 539, Folder 1)
    - General. Improvement Factor. New York Wage Increase Hearing. Carriers' Exhibit B, 1953 (Box 539, Folder 2)
    - General. Improvement Factor. New York Wage Increase Hearing. Carriers' Exhibit C, 1953 (Box 539, Folder 3)
    - General. Improvement Factor. New York Wage Increase Hearing. Carriers' Exhibit D, 1953 (Box 539, Folder 4)
    - General. Expenses Chargeable to Cooperative Wage Fund, 1950 Wage Movement, 1950-1953 (Box 539, Folder 5)
    - General. 1950 Wage Movement Conversion Factor. Case No. A-3605, 1953-1955 (Box 539, Folder 6)
    - General. 1950 Wage Movement Conversion Factor. Case No. A-3605, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 7)
      March 23, 1951-December 1951.
    - General. 1950 Wage Movement Conversion Factor. Circulars. Case No. A-3605, 1950-1951 (Box 539, Folder 8)
    - General. 1950 Wage Movement Conversion Factor. Case No. A-3605, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 9)
      March 4-22, 1951.
    - General. 1950 Wage Movement Conversion Factor. Case No. A-3605, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 10)
      January 19, 1951-March 3, 1951.
    - General. 1950 Wage Movement Conversion Factor. Case No. A-3605, 1950-1951 (Box 539, Folder 11)
      1950-January 18, 1951.
    - General. 1950 Wage Movement Conversion Factor. Special File. Case No. A-3605, 1950-1951 (Box 539, Folder 12)
    - General. Conference Material for National Negotiations on Wage Proposals, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 13)
      1951 January
    - General. Emergency Board Hearing. Wage Increase and Union Shop Disputes. Employees' Exhibits 31-40, 1943 (Box 540, Folder 1)
    - General. Emergency Board Hearing. Wage Increase and Union Shop Disputes. Employees' Exhibits 21-30, 1943 (Box 540, Folder 2)
    - General. Emergency Board Hearing. Wage Increase and Union Shop Disputes. Employees' Exhibits 18-20, 1943 (Box 540, Folder 3)
    - General. Emergency Board Hearing. Wage Increase and Union Shop Disputes. Employees' Exhibits 13-17, 1943 (Box 540, Folder 4)
    - General. Emergency Board Hearing. Wage Increase and Union Shop Disputes. Employees' Exhibits 10-12, 1943 (Box 540, Folder 5)
    - General. Emergency Board Hearing. Wage Increase and Union Shop Disputes. Employees' Exhibits 5-9, 1943 (Box 540, Folder 6)
    - General. Emergency Board Hearing. Wage Increase and Union Shop Disputes. Employees' Exhibits 5-9, 1943 (Box 540, Folder 7)
    - General. Emergency Board Hearing. Wage Increase and Union Shop Disputes. Employees' Exhibits 1-4, 1943 (Box 540, Folder 8)
    - General. National Railway Labor Panel Emergency Board Hearing on Wage Increases and Union Shop. Brief of Railway Labor Organizations., 1943 (Box 541, Folder 1)
      1943 April
    - General. National Railway Labor Panel Emergency Board Hearing on Wage Increases and Union Shop. Proceedings. vols.1-33, 1943 (Box 541, Folder 2)
    - General. National Railway Labor Panel Emergency Board Hearing on Wage Increases and Union Shop. Proceedings. vols.34-44, Briefs, Emergency Board Reports, 1943 (Box 541, Folder 3)
    - General. National Railway Labor Panel Emergency Board Hearing on Wage Increases and Union Shop. Proceedings. Index, Subsequent Developments, 1943 (Box 541, Folder 4)
    - General. National Railway Labor Panel Emergency Board Hearing on Wage Increases and Union Shop. Employees' Exhibits Nos. 73-122, 1943 (Box 541, Folder 5)
    - General. National Railway Labor Panel Emergency Board Hearing on Wage Increases and Union Shop. Employees' Exhibits Nos. 50-72, 1943 (Box 541, Folder 6)
    - General. National Railway Labor Panel Emergency Board Hearing on Wage Increases and Union Shop. Employees' Exhibits Nos. 41-49, 1943 (Box 541, Folder 7)
    - General. National Railway Labor Panel Emergency Board Hearing on Wage Increases and Union Shop. Briefs for Carriers, 1943 (Box 542, Folder 1)
    - General. National Railway Labor Panel Emergency Board Hearing on Wage Increases and Union Shop. Carriers' Exhibits Nos. 1-15, 1943 (Box 542, Folder 2)
    - General. National Railway Labor Panel Emergency Board Hearing on Wage Increases and Union Shop. Carriers' Exhibits Nos. 16-47, 1943 (Box 542, Folder 3)
    - General. National Railway Labor Panel Emergency Board Hearing on Wage Increases and Union Shop. Carriers' Exhibits Nos. 71-95a, 1943 (Box 542, Folder 4)
    - General. National Railway Labor Panel Emergency Board Hearing on Wage Increases and Union Shop. Carriers' Exhibits Nos. 95b-112, 1943 (Box 542, Folder 5)
    - General. Ore Dock Wage Increase Request, 1950 (Box 543, Folder 1)
    - General. Case No. A-2386, 1948 Rules and Wage Movement, Short Lines. Employees' Exhibit No. 15. "Relevancy of Employer's Ability to Pay in Wage Determinations", 1946 (Box 543, Folder 2)
    - General. Case No. A-2386, 1948 Rules and Wage Movement, Short Lines, 1946-1947 (Box 543, Folder 3)
    - General. Case No. A-2386, 1948 Rules and Wage Movement, Short Lines, 1947 (Box 543, Folder 4)
      August-October 1947.
    - General. Case No. A-2386, 1948 Rules and Wage Movement, Short Lines. Circulars., 1950 (Box 543, Folder 5)
    - General. Case No. A-2386, 1948 Rules and Wage Movement, Short Lines. Complete Set of Employees' Exhibits., 1947 (Box 543, Folder 6)
    - General. Case No. A-2386, 1948 Rules and Wage Movement, Short Lines, 1947-1948 (Box 543, Folder 7)
      November 1947-March 1948.
    - General. Case No. A-2386, 1948 Rules and Wage Movement, Short Lines, 1947 (Box 543, Folder 8)
      March-July 1947.
    - General. Case No. A-2386, 1948 Rules and Wage Movement, Short Lines. Brief of Carriers., 1947 (Box 543, Folder 9)
      1947 August 27
    - General. Case No. A-2386, 1948 Rules and Wage Movement, Short Lines. Brief of Railway Labor Organizations., 1947 (Box 543, Folder 10)
      1947 August 28
    - General. Case No. A-2386, 1948 Rules and Wage Movement, Short Lines. Employees' Exhibits. (Box 543, Folder 11)
    - General. Case No. A-2386, 1948 Rules and Wage Movement, Short Lines. Proceedings. (Box 543, Folder 12)
      1948 January 6
    - General. Case No. A-2386, 1948 Rules and Wage Movement, Short Lines. Proceedings. (Box 543, Folder 13)
      1948 January 12
    - General. Case No. A-2386, 1948 Rules and Wage Movement, Short Lines. Proceedings. (Box 544, Folder 1)
      1948 January 16
    - General. Special Wage File, 1946 (Box 544, Folder 2)
      May 1-28, 1946.
    - General. Special Wage File, 1946 (Box 544, Folder 3)
      March-April 1946.
    - General. Special Wage File, 1946 (Box 544, Folder 4)
      January-February 1946.
    - General. 1964 Canadian Wage and Rules Movement. Notice of November 1, 1963, 1963-1964 (Box 544, Folder 5)
      October 1963-July 1964.
    - General. 1961 Canadian Wage Movement, 1961-1963 (Box 544, Folder 6)
    - General. 1959 Joint Wage and Rules Movement, 1959-1961 (Box 544, Folder 7)
    - General. 1957 Canadian Wage Movement, 1959 (Box 544, Folder 8)
    - General. 1957 Canadian Wage Movement, 1957-1958 (Box 544, Folder 9)
    - General. 1957 Canadian Wage Movement. Submission on Behalf of Railway Employees to Board of Conciliation and Investigation, 1958 (Box 544, Folder 10)
      1958 February
    - General. 1957 Canadian Wage Movement. Submission on Behalf of Railway Employees to Board of Conciliation and Investigation, 1958 (Box 545, Folder 1)
    - General. Canada, 1954-1958 (Box 545, Folder 2)
      January 1954-58.
    - General. 1955-1956 Canadian Wage Movement (Box 545, Folder 3)
    - General. Canada, 1950-1953 (Box 545, Folder 4)
      October 1950-53.
    - General. Canada, 1950 (Box 545, Folder 5)
      August 17, 1950-September 1950.
    - General. Canada, 1949-1950 (Box 545, Folder 6)
      1949-August 16, 1950.
    - General. 1948 Wage Movement. Report of Emergency Board, NMB Case No. A-2953 (Box 545, Folder 7)
      1948 December 17
    - General. 1948 Wage Movement. Emergency Board, NMB Case No. A-2953. Brief of Railway Labor Organizations. (Box 545, Folder 8)
      1948 November 27
    - General. 1948 Wage Movement. Emergency Board, NMB Case No. A-2953. Brief of Carriers (Box 545, Folder 9)
      1948 November 29
    - General. 1948 Wage Movement. Emergency Board, NMB Case No. A-2953. Brief., 1950-1957 (Box 545, Folder 10)
      May 25, 1950-57.
    - General. 1948 Wage Movement. Emergency Board, NMB Case No. A-2953, 1950 (Box 545, Folder 11)
      March 16, 1950-May 24, 1950.
    - General. 1948 Wage Movement. Emergency Board, NMB Case No. A-2953. Complete Set of Circular Letters., 1949-1950 (Box 545, Folder 12)
      April 1949-50.
    - General. 1948 Wage Movement. Emergency Board, NMB Case No. A-2953. 40-Hour Week, 1949-1950 (Box 546, Folder 1)
      November 1949-50.
    - General. 1948 Wage Movement. Emergency Board, NMB Case No. A-2953. 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 546, Folder 2)
      December 1948-October 1949.
    - General. 1948 Wage Movement. Emergency Board, NMB Case No. A-2953. 40-Hour Week (Box 546, Folder 3)
      October-November 1948.
    - General. 1948 Wage Movement. Emergency Board, NMB Case No. A-2953. 40-Hour Week (Box 546, Folder 4)
      March-September 1948.
    - General. 1948 Wage Movement. Emergency Board, NMB Case No. A-2953, 1949-1950 (Box 546, Folder 5)
      September 1949-March 15, 1950.
    - General. 1948 Wage Movement. Emergency Board, NMB Case No. A-2953, 1949 (Box 546, Folder 6)
      April 16, 1949-August 1949.
    - General. 1948 Wage Movement. Emergency Board, NMB Case No. A-2953, 1949 (Box 546, Folder 7)
      January 1949-April 15, 1949.
    - General. 1948 Wage Movement. Emergency Board, NMB Case No. A-2953, 1948-1949 (Box 546, Folder 8)
      1948-March 1949.
    - General. 1948 Wage Movement. Emergency Board, NMB Case No. A-2953 (Box 546, Folder 9)
    - General. 1941 Emergency Board Case on Wages, Rules and Vacations. Complete Set of Circular Letters (Box 546, Folder 10)
    - General. 1941 Emergency Board Case on Wages, Rules and Vacations. List of Exhibits (Box 546, Folder 11)
      September-October 1941.
    - General. 1941 Emergency Board Case on Wages, Rules and Vacations. Appendix to Transcript of Proceedings (Box 546, Folder 12)
    - General. 1941 Emergency Board Case on Wages, Rules and Vacations. Exhibits (Box 547, Folder 1)
    - General. 1941 Emergency Board Case on Wages, Rules and Vacations. Carriers' Brief (Box 547, Folder 2)
      1941 October 20
    - General. 1941 Emergency Board Case on Wages, Rules and Vacations. Carriers' Brief (Box 547, Folder 3)
      1941 October 18
    - General. 1941 Emergency Board Case on Wages, Rules and Vacations. Employees' Brief (Box 547, Folder 4-5)
    - General. 1941 Emergency Board Case on Wages, Rules and Vacations. Mediation Settlement (Box 547, Folder 6-7)
    - General. 1941 Emergency Board Case on Wages, Rules and Vacations. "Facts for Use by General Chairmen in Support of Request for Increase in Rates of Pay" (Box 547, Folder 8)
      1941 June
    - General. 1941 Emergency Board Case on Wages, Rules and Vacations. Employees' Exhibit (Box 547, Folder 9)
      1941 September
    - General. 1941 Emergency Board Case on Wages, Rules and Vacations. Carriers' Exhibit No. 163. "Federal Legislation" (Box 547, Folder 10)
    - General. 1941 Emergency Board Case on Wages, Rules and Vacations. Carriers' Exhibit No. 162. "State Legislation" (Box 547, Folder 11)
    - General. 1941 Emergency Board Case on Wages, Rules and Vacations. Transcript (Box 547, Folder 12)
      July 29, 1941-August 5, 1941.
    - General. Minutes of Meetings Held by Brotherhood and Non-Operating Brotherhood General Chairmen, 1941 (Box 547, Folder 13)
      November 12-13, 1941.
    - General. Records Showing Basic Rates of Pay. Train and Engine Service Employees, 1941 (Box 547, Folder 14)
      1920-September 1, 1941.
    - General. Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1932 (Box 547, Folder 15)
      January 13, 1932-February 1, 1932.
    - General. "Railway Labor", 1932 (Box 547, Folder 16)
      1932 December 12
    - General. National Wage Conference. Complete Set of Exchanges of Letters, Statements, Proposals, Counter-Proposals and Final Agreement With Letter Re-Interpretation, 1932 (Box 547, Folder 17)
      December 12-22, 1932.
    - General. National Wage Conference. Report, 1932 (Box 547, Folder 18-19)
    - General. "Historical Development of the Present Railroad Wage Structure: 1916-1938" (Box 547, Folder 20)
      1938 September
    - General. Statisticians' Material on Rebuttal of Carriers' Wage Arguments, 1938 (Box 547, Folder 21)
    - General. 1941 Emergency Board Case on Wages, Rules and Vacations. Employees' Brief (Box 547, Folder 22-23)
    - General. 1941 Emergency Board Case on Wages, Rules and Vacations. Report to the President (Box 547, Folder 24-25)
      1941 November 5
    - General. 1941 Emergency Board Case on Wages, Rules and Vacations. Brief of Western and Southwestern Carriers Regarding Rules Changes for the Non-Operating Crafts (Box 547, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 408-1. Wages
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1944-1954 (Box 548, Folder 1)
    - Atlantic Coast Line. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 548, Folder 2)
    - Atlantic Coast Line. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 548, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 408-2. Wages
    - Illinois Central Railroad, 1944-1953 (Box 548, Folder 4)
    - Illinois Central Railroad. Hospital Department. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 548, Folder 5)
    - Illinois Central Railroad. Hospital Department. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 548, Folder 6)
    - Illinois Central Railroad. Hospital Department. Case No. A-4032, 1951-1953 (Box 548, Folder 7)
    - Illinois Central Railroad. Case No. A-1559. Panel Board Hearing Transcripts. Vol. 1, 1947 (Box 548, Folder 8)
      1947 March 3
    - Illinois Central Railroad. Case No. A-1559. Panel Board Hearing Transcripts. Vol. 2, 1947 (Box 548, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 408-3. Wages
    - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1947-1953 (Box 548, Folder 10)
    - Lehigh Valley Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 548, Folder 11)
    - Lehigh Valley Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 548, Folder 12)
    - Lehigh Valley Railroad. Case No. A-3276, 1949-1950 (Box 548, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 408-4. Wages
    - Delaware and Hudson Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 548, Folder 14)
    - Delaware and Hudson Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 548, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 408-5. Wages
    - Charleston and Western Carolina Railway, 1943-1961 (Box 548, Folder 16)
    - Charleston and Western Carolina Railway. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 548, Folder 17)
    - Charleston and Western Carolina Railway. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 548, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 408-6. Wages
    - Cincinnati, Indianapolis and Western Railroad, 1952 (Box 548, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 408-8. Wages
    - Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad, 1937-1950 (Box 548, Folder 20)
    - Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad, 1954-1955 (Box 548, Folder 21)
    - Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 548, Folder 22)
    - Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 548, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 408-9. Wages
    - Louisiana and Arkansas Railway. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 548, Folder 24)
    - Louisiana and Arkansas Railway. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 548, Folder 25)
    - Louisiana and Arkansas Railway. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 548, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 408-11. Wages
    - Bangor and Aroostook Railroad, 1954-1956 (Box 548, Folder 27)
    - Bangor and Aroostook Railroad, 1931-1953 (Box 548, Folder 28)
    - Bangor and Aroostook Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 548, Folder 29)
    - Bangor and Aroostook Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 548, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 408-12. Wages
    - Michigan Central Railroad, 1953-1955 (Box 548, Folder 31)
    - Michigan Central Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 548, Folder 32)
    - Michigan Central Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 548, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 408-13. Wages
    - Central of Georgia, 1946-1951 (Box 548, Folder 34)
    - Central of Georgia. 1956 Wage Movement. Clerks and Miscellaneous Employees, 1956-1957 (Box 548, Folder 35)
    - Central of Georgia. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 549, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 408-14. Wages
    - Louisville and Nashville Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 549, Folder 2)
    - Louisville and Nashville Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 549, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 408-15. Wages
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railroad, 1951-1955 (Box 549, Folder 4)
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railroad, 1949-1950 (Box 549, Folder 5)
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement. Gulf, Colorado, and Santa Fe Railway; Panhandle and Santa Fe Railway; Dining Car Department; Laundry Workers; Tie and Timber Treating Plants, Somerville, Texas and Albuquerque, New Mexico. 1956 (Box 549, Folder 6)
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 549, Folder 7)
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railroad. Case No. A-2635, 1947-1953 (Box 549, Folder 8)
      June 1947-53.
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railroad. Current and Proposed Rates of Pay, 1951 (Box 549, Folder 9)
      1951 June 30
  - Sub-Series 408-17. Wages
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Minneapolis, Minnesota. Case No. A-4358, 1953-1955 (Box 549, Folder 10)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Negro Issues. Case No. A-4358, 1953-1954 (Box 549, Folder 11)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. New Orleans, Louisiana. Case No. A-4358, 1953-1954 (Box 549, Folder 12)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. New York, New York. Case No. A-4358, 1953-1955 (Box 549, Folder 13)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Oakland, California. Case No. A-4358, 1953-1954 (Box 549, Folder 14)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. 1961 Wage Movement, 1961-1963 (Box 549, Folder 15)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Canada. 1963 Wage Movement (Box 549, Folder 16)
      1963 November, 1
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Wage Adjustment. Hollywood, California; San Diego, California, 1960 (Box 549, Folder 17)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. General, 1957-1963 (Box 549, Folder 18)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. General, 1953-1956 (Box 549, Folder 19)
      December 1953-56.
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. General, 1948-1953 (Box 549, Folder 20)
      June 1948-November 1953.
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Canada, 1952-1957 (Box 549, Folder 21)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Canada. 1959 Wage Movement, 1961 (Box 549, Folder 22)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Canada, 1938-1951 (Box 549, Folder 23)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. 15% Reduction, 1938-1939 (Box 550, Folder 1)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Agreements, 1944-1949 (Box 550, Folder 2)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. National Wage Increase Movement. Emergency Board, 1941-1942 (Box 550, Folder 3)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc., 1932-1936 (Box 550, Folder 4)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. 1961 Wage Movement. Mediation Cases Nos. A-6720 and A-6730 (Box 550, Folder 5)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. 1961 Wage Case (Box 550, Folder 6)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. 1960 Wage Movement (Box 550, Folder 7)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. 1963 Wage Movement. Letters Concerning Ballots Forwarded with Circular Letter Dated March 20, 1964, 1963-1964 (Box 550, Folder 8)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Emergency Board Report Regarding Carrier's Dispute with International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Locals 808 and 459, 1950 (Box 550, Folder 9)
      1950 November 2
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Detroit, Michigan. Case No. A-4279, 1953-1957 (Box 550, Folder 10)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. 1950 Wage Movement. Case No. A-3602, 1950-1951 (Box 550, Folder 11)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. Case No. A-4295, 1953-1956 (Box 550, Folder 12)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Saginaw, Michigan. 1956 Wage Adjustment (Box 550, Folder 13)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Alhambra, California; Burbank, California; Downey, California; Hollywood, California; Long Beach, California; Los Angeles, California; Pasadena, California; Redondo Beach, California; San Pedro, California; Santa Monica, Calif, 1956-1957 (Box 550, Folder 14)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. 1956 Wage Movement. Mediation Case No. A-5224 (Box 550, Folder 15)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 550, Folder 16)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4812, 1955-1956 (Box 551, Folder 1)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4812, 1955 (Box 551, Folder 2)
      February 9-18, 1955.
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. General, 1954-1956 (Box 551, Folder 3)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Chicago, Illinois, 1953-1955 (Box 551, Folder 4)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Cincinnati, Ohio, 1953-1955 (Box 551, Folder 5)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. East St. Louis, Illinois, 1953-1955 (Box 551, Folder 6)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Kansas City, Missouri, 1953-1955 (Box 551, Folder 7)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Memphis, Tennessee, 1953-1954 (Box 551, Folder 8)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1953-1956 (Box 551, Folder 9)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Pontiac, Michigan, 1953-1954 (Box 551, Folder 10)